[Strings]
intro_title = "NEW MOMBASA, EAST AFRICAN PROTECTORATE"
dig_eula = "This scenario is a composite recreation of the 2003 prototype|n''Earth City'', assembled from archive data, internal research and |nour own restorative work to showcase early Halo 2 development.|n|nIntended to be played as a rehearsed demonstration, mission|nelements do not account for deviation of expected, scripted|n gameplay sequences. Your play experience may vary.|n|nLaunch with A / ENTER when ready."
dig_advice = ">> Cue guides are ENABLED. <<|n Visible waypoints will mark where/when to progress the mission as originally rehearsed"
dig_booth = "WELCOME TO HCS!|n|nDEMO MODE is enabled,|nYour battle suit will automatically indicate|nthe intended path to recreate the demo|nsequence, as played in 2003.|n|nThis build is not representative of|nfinal release. Your experience may vary.|n|n - DIGSITE TEAM -"
dig_freedom = "freedom"
dig_offcue = "RETURN TO THE BATTLEFIELD.|nProgressing further from the demo mission cues will reset to last checkpoint."
dig_subtitles = "Subtitles have been created for all dialog lines.|nCheck your game settings to enable them."
dig_waypoints = "test"
dig_button_start = "Press JUMP to continue, and launch the mission|n|nPress FLASHLIGHT to explore the world with all scripts disabled."
dig_moth_1 = "GUIDE WAYPOINTS ON|n|n(SWITCH WEAPON to disable guide points.)|nYour HUD indicates next points of interest"
dig_moth_0 = "GUIDE WAYPOINTS OFF|n|n(SWITCH WEAPON to enable guide points.)|nYour HUD will not indicate next points of interest."
dig_freedom_1 = "SANDBOX MODE ON|n|n(SWITCH GRENADES to toggle scripts.)|nYou can freely explore the world."
dig_freedom_0 = "SANDBOX MODE OFF|n|n(SWITCH GRENADES to toggle scripts.)|nGoing off-script may break the mission."